Every time we eat here, your mom refuses
to let me help with the dishes.
(Howard:)Don't take it personally.
(Howard:)She likes doing them by herself so she can
lick the plates with no one looking.
(Bernadette:)You ready to go?
(Howard:)Yeah, let me just grab a couple
of fresh turtlenecks.
(Bernadette:)I don't understand why you keep your stuff
here when there's room at home.
(Howard:)What are you talking about?
(Howard:)All I have here is a few sweaters,
books, bank stuff...
(Howard:)...computers, mail, collectibles, medicine
and my electric body groomer.
Ooh! There's my plaid dickey.
(Howard:)Oh. Got this at the Goodwill store for 50 cents.
Can you believe it? Heh.
Fifty cents sounds right.
(Bernadette:)- Let's go.
- You know, it's kind of late.
- Why don't we spend the night here?
- Because we don't live here.
(Sheldon:)- I know.
- Do you?
(Bernadette:)You said when you got back from space...
(Bernadette:)...you were gonna move into my apartment,
but half the time we stay here.